www511456.com 2011-12-31

# www.com — the web starts here

## Privacy Policy

### Our Privacy Commitment to You

At [WWW.com](http://www.com/), through its owner and manager Original Web Ventures Inc., it is our goal to protect the privacy of our consumers. We are dedicated to providing a safe and secure environment for our consumers' information.   
This Privacy Policy governs Personal Information collected from individuals by [WWW.com](http://www.com/), including information collected through [WWW.com](http://www.com/) branded pages. Our pages are clearly marked with our, and any of our co-branded websites', logos. It is understood that we may offer short-cuts, links or references to other companies and organizations, however, this policy does not apply to those sites. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of these external sites for further information.

### Why [WWW.com](http://www.com/) collects Personal Information

For the purposes of this Policy, we consider "Personal Information" to mean information, recorded in any format, about an identified individual, or an individual whose identity may be inferred or determined from the information. [WWW.com](http://www.com/) only collects, uses and discloses Personal Information where it is considered reasonable in the circumstances and for purposes required to provide our services.   
Generally, the only information we collect is information that is voluntarily provided by you as part of the registration or membership process. [WWW.com](http://www.com/)'s use of Personal Information is limited to these purposes or is consistent with them. We do not pass on any Personal Information to any of our linked sites or merchants. Those sites are responsible for collecting their own information as needed. [WWW.com](http://www.com/) does not sell, trade, barter, exchange or disclose for consideration any Personal Information it has obtained. Unless permitted by law, no Personal Information is collected about a member or client without first obtaining the consent of the individual to the collection, use and dissemination of that information.

### Use of Cookies

[WWW.com](http://www.com/) may also collect information through the use of cookies (computer software that allows communication between your computer and [WWW.com](http://www.com/)). These cookies are used to determine the number and frequency of visits to [WWW.com](http://www.com/) sites. The data collected is aggregated and does not allow [WWW.com](http://www.com/) to identify you personally, unless you voluntarily offer such information. We collect information through cookies so that we may provide ratings and information to advertisers and partners to indicate how frequently customers visit our site and their sections.   
[WWW.com](http://www.com/) may also collect information to enhance and improve the quality of our sites. Such information may include IP addresses, ISPs, and browser type. Again, this information is collected in an aggregate format to track user patterns, movement, general clickthrough trends and for reporting and advertising purposes.   
Third party advertisers may also use cookies to gather information about visits to their sites. Any such information collected, whether voluntarily or through the use of cookies, is not the responsibility of [WWW.com](http://www.com/). [WWW.com](http://www.com/) strongly encourages you to read and review the privacy policies of all external and linked sites to understand your rights and exposure.

### Your consent

**Your provision of Personal Information to[WWW.com](http://www.com/) means that you agree and consent that we may collect, use and disclose your Personal Information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.** In addition, specific authorizations or consents may be obtained from time to time.  
In most cases, and subject to legal and contractual restrictions, you are free to refuse or withdraw your consent at any time upon reasonable, advance notice by contacting [WWW.com](http://www.com/) as indicated at the end of this Policy. You should note that certain services can only be offered if an individual provides Personal Information to [WWW.com](http://www.com/) and, consequently, if an individual chooses not to provide us with the required Personal Information, we may not be able to offer the services requested. We will, however, at the time of withdrawal, inform you of the consequences of such a withdrawal of consent.   
You also have the option of cancelling or updating your current personal profile at any time through the [WWW.com](http://www.com/) site by logging into your profile and following the instructions on-screen.

### How we use your Personal Information

[WWW.com](http://www.com/) uses Personal Information in the normal course of providing its services, which may include activities such as: 

  * registering domains;
  * opening email accounts;
  * hosting websites;
  * providing customer service and solutions; 
  * searching the web;
  * registering with search engines; and
  * engaging in other related activities and services. 

### When can [WWW.com](http://www.com/) disclose your Personal Information

There are circumstances where the use and/or disclosure of Personal Information may be justified or permitted or where [WWW.com](http://www.com/) is obliged to disclose information without consent. Such circumstances may include:

  * Where required by law or by subpoena, warrant, court order or the order of a tribunal;
  * Where [WWW.com](http://www.com/) believes, upon reasonable grounds, that it is necessary to protect the rights, privacy, safety or property of an identifiable person or group; 
  * Where it is necessary to establish or collect fees; 
  * Where it is necessary to permit us to pursue available remedies or limit any damages that we may sustain; and
  * Where the information is public;
  * Where obliged or permitted to disclose Personal Information without consent, [WWW.com](http://www.com/) will not disclose more information than is required.

[WWW.com](http://www.com/) will only disclose Personal Information about former clients in accordance with this Privacy Policy. [WWW.com](http://www.com/) retains the right to use non-identifiable information in any ethical way that it determines appropriate.

### Disclosure to Third Parties

[WWW.com](http://www.com/) will not share any Personal Information with anyone, including third parties, without your consent. Users have the option of granting permission within any product or membership registration area. Again, this site may contain shortcuts, by way of links or references, to other websites. Please be aware that [WWW.com](http://www.com/) does not control other Websites and that, in any case, this Privacy Policy does not apply to those websites.   
Please remember that what you write or publish in the public areas on any of our sites is visible to the public and that the information can be seen and used by others. [WWW.com](http://www.com/) is not responsible for the release of any such voluntarily released information. While [WWW.com](http://www.com/) is dedicated to respecting and maintaining your privacy rights, posting and submitting such Personal Information in public forums is done at the user's risk. In addition, it is important that you keep your passwords secure and stay informed by reading this Privacy Policy, as well as the privacy policies of partners, advertisers, and merchants. 

### The accuracy and retention of Personal Information

[WWW.com](http://www.com/) endeavours to ensure that any Personal Information in its possession is as accurate, current and complete as necessary for the purposes for which [WWW.com](http://www.com/) uses that data. Information contained in files that have been closed is not actively updated or maintained. [WWW.com](http://www.com/) generally retains Personal Information as long as [WWW.com](http://www.com/) believes it is necessary to fulfil the purpose for which it was collected. Currently, the principal place in which [WWW.com](http://www.com/) holds your Personal Information is in the City of Ottawa and nearby municipalities where off-site storage facilities may be located.

### Protection of Personal Information

[WWW.com](http://www.com/) endeavours to maintain adequate physical, procedural and technical security with respect to its offices and information storage facilities so as to prevent any loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, or modification of Personal Information. This also applies to our disposal or destruction of Personal Information.  
As part of those precautions, we restrict access to Personal Information to those employees and external service providers we determine need to know that information in order that [WWW.com](http://www.com/) may provide its sevices. [WWW.com](http://www.com/) has a policy under which employee misuse of Personal Information is treated as a serious offence for which disciplinary action may be taken.  
Where required, www.com may also engage other service providers located in the United States. Therefore, some of your personal information may be retained in the United States where privacy laws may offer different levels of protection from those in Canada and your personal information may be subject to access by and disclosure to law enforcement agencies under American legislation such as the USA Patriot Act.   
We audit our procedures and security measures from time to time to ensure that they remain effective and appropriate.

### Accessing Your Personal Information

[WWW.com](http://www.com/) allows you to access and review your Personal Information held by us and will endeavour to provide the Personal Information in question within a reasonable time, generally no later than 30 days following the request. There may be a charge for retrieving a complete list of Personal Information, in which case you will be notified in advance and you may, at that time, withdraw your request. 

### Changes to the Privacy Policy

[WWW.com](http://www.com/) strives to maintain an up-to-date and current Privacy Policy. If any changes are made to the Policy, such changes are posted on this page. By checking this page frequently, individuals can remain aware of [WWW.com](http://www.com/)'s collection, use and disclosure policies. 

### Questions or Concerns

Questions regarding this Privacy Policy should be directed to Original Web Ventures Inc. by sending an email to:  
[legaldept@WWW.com](mailto:legaldept@WWW.com) or [support@www.com](mailto:support@www.com)   
Or by contacting:   
Original Web Ventures Inc., owner and executive manager of the [WWW.com](http://www.com/) website  
2 Bradley Farm Crt.,   
Kanata, ON, K2L 4B5  
Canada 

[WWW.com](http://www.com/) will investigate all complaints and if a complaint is justified, we will take all reasonable steps to resolve the issue.

Updated Dec 5 2007
